mbaskool.com 2019-06-04

# Privacy Policy | MBA Skool-Study.Learn.Share.

**Privacy & Cookie Policy for mbaskool.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [admin@mbaskool.com](mailto:admin@mbaskool.com).

At mbaskool.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by mbaskool.com and how it is used.

Following are the scenarios where we use cookies and may ask for personal information : 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

mbaskool.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

To make mbaskool.com work properly, we sometimes place small data files called cookies on your device.

 **What are cookies?**

A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another.

mbaskool.com uses analytics services for understanding the visitors. We use this service to better understanding how our visitors interact with our website so that we can improve our services and offer better features.

 **Analytics**

We use following for analytics and traffic analysis

 **1\. Google Analytics**

We use Google analytics for anaylizing traffic trends and other information like unique users, time spent, browser and OS info, device info etc. 

You can refer to  <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites> for more details.  

 **2\. Statcounter**  

Statcounter services uses cookies to enable us to analyse visitors and activity. 

You can learn more about cookies from StatCounter and set your browser to refuse same by clicking on http://statcounter.com/about/set-refusal-cookie/.

For further details, please see the Statcounter privacy policy (<https://statcounter.com/about/legal/#privacy>).

**Advertising**

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on mbaskool.com.

.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to mbaskool.com and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URLs -

<https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>  

<https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....

**Google Adsense**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on mbaskool.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

 **Recommendations (Including Sponsored/Promoted Content)**

We use Outbrain for recommendations (including sponsored) on our website. You can visit <https://www.outbrain.com/legal/privacy> for more details and chose to Opt out using <https://www.outbrain.com/legal/privacy#advertising_behavioral_targeting>

mbaskool.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, mbaskool.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **User Signup & Submissions**

We may use the information we collect from our users to set up user account and to enable login. We do not sell your Personal Information to anyone.

We collect personal information only when needed e.g.

1) Signup form

2) Submission and content forms

we make sure that the information is only asked if necessary and the personal data is not used apart from the intended use i.e. contacting back for the status of the request or submission.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. mbaskool.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**How to control cookies**

You can control (or disable & delete) cookies. Please visit [aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) for details. You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

 **Updated on : May 2018**
